Driven to Hell
Road Train is a horror, thriller, science fiction film directed by Dean Francis.
A supernatural thriller about a group of teenagers menaced by a
driver-less train in the Australian outback.
Marcus, played by Xavier Samuel.
Craig, played by Bob Morley.
Liz, played by Georgina Haig.
Nina, played by Sophie Lowe.
Psycho, played by David Argue.
Road Kill, known as Road Train in Australia, is a 2010 Australian horror
film directed by Dean Francis and written by Clive Hopkins.
It stars Xavier Samuel, Bobby Morley, Georgina Haig and Sophie Lowe.
The film explores themes of chase, truck, descent
into madness, australian outback.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.